Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)
  - Clinical Hospital Facilities, 1893 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00005; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00044; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, pediatric orthopedic ward, UA225.004.001.00005.00045; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Hospital units; Pediatrics; Nurses; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, pediatric orthopedic ward, UA225.004.001.00005.00046; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Hospital units; Pediatrics; Traction; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Dowling Amphitheatre, UA225.004.001.00005.00047; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Auditoriums; Internship and residency; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Dr. Paul O'Brien with residents and students at Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00048; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Internship and Residency; Slides (photographs); O'Brien, Paul I.; Boston City Hospital
    - Dr. Henry Banks with Cotton bust, UA225.004.001.00005.00049; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Busts (sculpture); Deans (Education); Physicians; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Cotton, Frederic Jay (1869-1938); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston Veterans Administration, UA225.004.001.00005.00050; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Hospitals, Veterans; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Boston Veterans Administration, Outpatient Clinic, UA225.004.001.00005.00051; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Hospitals, Veterans; Teaching Hospitals; Outpatient Clinics, Hospital; Slides (photographs)
    - Robert Brent Brigham Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00052; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Old Robert Brent Brigham Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00053; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Old Carney Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00054; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Dorcester (Mass.); Buildings; Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - New Carney Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00055; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Cushing Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00056; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Cushing Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00057; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Faulkner Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00058; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Faulkner Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00059; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Faulkner Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00060; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Kennedy Memorial Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00061; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Kennedy Memorial Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00062; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Kennedy Memorial Hospital, Joseph Kennedy, Jr., UA225.004.001.00005.00063; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - West Roxbury Veterans Administration Hosptial, UA225.004.001.00005.00064; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Hospitals, Veterans; Slides (photographs)
    - Lakeville Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00065; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Lakeville (Mass.); Buildings; Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Lakeville Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00066; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Maine Medical Center, UA225.004.001.00005.00067; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Maine.; Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Mass Hospital School at Canton, UA225.004.001.00005.00068; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Canton (Mass.); Buildings; Hospitals, Pediatric; Slides (photographs)
    - Massachusetts General Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00069; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - New England Baptist Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00070; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - New England Baptist Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00071; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - New England Baptist Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00072; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00073; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00074; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - St. Luke's Hospital, New Bedford, UA225.004.001.00005.00075; Tufts University (Box 1)
      New Bedfor (Mass.); Buildings; Hospitals; Slides (photographs)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00076; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, 1938; UA225.004.001.00005.00077; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00078; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00079; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - TUSM, 1893 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00005.00080; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Medical colleges; Organization and administration; Slides (photographs); School of Medicine
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Students, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00081; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical education; Slides (photographs); School of Medicine
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Faculty, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00082; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Education, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00083; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Research, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00084; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Finances, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00085; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Relationships, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00086; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Issues facing medical education, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00087; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Strategy Audit, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00088; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Visiting Committee Presentation, Strategy Audit, 1987-02; UA225.004.001.00005.00089; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dean's Office Organization, UA225.004.001.00005.00090; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); School of Medicine
    - Development of TUSM plant, UA225.004.001.00005.00091; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Timelines of American history; Teaching Hospitals; Buildings; Slides (photographs); School of Medicine
    - Development of TUSM plant, UA225.004.001.00005.00092; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Timelines of American history; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); School of Medicine
    - Development of New England Medical Center facilities, UA225.004.001.00005.00093; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Timelines of American history; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Formation of T-NEMC, UA225.004.001.00005.00094; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Timelines of American history; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Reverend Rufus Tobey, Founder of Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00095; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Infants; Teaching Hospitals; Clergy; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Barge "Clifford" with Tug Boat, 1894 -- 1906; UA225.004.001.00005.00096; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Hospital ships; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00097; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Hospital ships; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Barge "Clifford" (left) with the new Boston Floating Hospital, 1906; UA225.004.001.00005.00098; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00099; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00100; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00101; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00102; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital Auto and Ship, UA225.004.001.00005.00103; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital nursing class, 1926; UA225.004.001.00005.00104; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Nursing; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Boston Floating Hospital wardon ship, UA225.004.001.00005.00105; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital patients aboard ship, UA225.004.001.00005.00106; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Patients; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital; Patients
    - Boarding the Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00107; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, patient ward on ship, UA225.004.001.00005.00108; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, babies' bottoms, UA225.004.001.00005.00109; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00110; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00111; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, patient line-up, UA225.004.001.00005.00112; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Patients; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Boston Floating Hospital, patients "on shore", UA225.004.001.00005.00113; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00114; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, 1894 -- 1931; UA225.004.001.00005.00115; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - New Boston Floating Hospital, laying the cornerstone, UA225.004.001.00005.00116; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, Jackson Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00117; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, 1931; UA225.004.001.00005.00118; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00119; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00120; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00121; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00122; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Land-Based Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00123; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Land-Based Boston Floating Hospital, timeline/baby, UA225.004.001.00005.00124; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, x-ray, UA225.004.001.00005.00125; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - BFH groundbreaking, Dr. Gellis, Miss Katz, Dr. Grossman, April Murphy, 1979-10-25; UA225.004.001.00005.00126; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New Boston Floating Hospital, air view, UA225.004.001.00005.00127; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center, 750 Washington St., UA225.004.001.00005.00128; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New Floating entrance, 750 Washington St., UA225.004.001.00005.00129; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Entrance to new Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00130; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Entrance to new Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00131; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, New England Medical Center, UA225.004.001.00005.00132; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00133; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Boston Floating Hospital, New England Medical Center, UA225.004.001.00005.00134; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Boston Dispensary, Pratt, UA225.004.001.00005.00135; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, 1938; UA225.004.001.00005.00136; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Pratt Diagnostic Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00137; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Pratt, UA225.004.001.00005.00138; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center, Farnsworth, UA225.004.001.00005.00139; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center, Farnsworth, UA225.004.001.00005.00140; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center, Farnsworth, UA225.004.001.00005.00141; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Proger Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00142; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center entrance, 750 Washington St., UA225.004.001.00005.00143; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Entrance halls; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - New England Medical Center entrance, 750 Wasington St., UA225.004.001.00005.00144; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - New England Medical Center entrance, 750 Wasington St., UA225.004.001.00005.00145; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Wang Center and Biewend Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00146; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Biewend Building entrance, UA225.004.001.00005.00147; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Wang Center marquee, UA225.004.001.00005.00148; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Marquees; Slides (photographs); Boston Campus
    - Tupper Research Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00149; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Research; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Washington St., looking south, UA225.004.001.00005.00150; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); School of Dental Medicine; Boston Floating Hospital; Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging; New England Medical Center
    - Nutrition Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00151; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Jean Mayer USDA Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging
    - Nutrition Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00152; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00153; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Construction projects; Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Slides (photographs)
    - Foundation of MRI unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00154; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Construction projects; Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Slides (photographs)
    - MRI Building and Seybolt Plaza, UA225.004.001.00005.00155; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Buildings; Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - Magnetic Resonance Imaging, UA225.004.001.00005.00156; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Slides (photographs); Boston Floating Hospital
    - MRI Building and Seybolt Plaza, UA225.004.001.00005.00157; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Magnetic Resonance Imaging, UA225.004.001.00005.00158; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Medical instruments and apparatus; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - MRI-NEMC, 1986; UA225.004.001.00005.00159; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - MRI of brain, UA225.004.001.00005.00160; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Magnetic Resonance Imaging; Brain; Slides (photographs)
    - Air view of Health Sciences campus, UA225.004.001.00005.00161; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buidings; Aerial views; Slides (photographs); Boston Campus
    - Tufts University, Boston Campus, UA225.004.001.00005.00162; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Signs and signboards; Slides (photographs); Boston Campus
    - NEMC aerial, 1983; UA225.004.001.00005.00163; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Boston (Mass.); Buidings; Aerial views; Slides (photographs); New England Medical Center
    - Air view of Health Sciences Campus, UA225.004.001.00005.00164; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Air view of Health Sciences Campus, UA225.004.001.00005.00165; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
  - Alumni, Accomplishments and Challenges, 1934 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00006; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Alumni, UA225.004.001.000006.00001; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs)
    - Typical alumnus on a house call, UA225.004.001.000006.00002; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - M '32 Pageant, UA225.004.001.000006.00003; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); M1932
    - M '34 reunion committee, UA225.004.001.000006.00004; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); M1934
    - M '34 25th reunion, UA225.004.001.000006.00005; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - United States and Tufts alumni in other professional activities, UA225.004.001.000006.00006; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Alumni faculty appointments, 1986; UA225.004.001.000006.00007; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Tufts academic alumni, 1990; UA225.004.001.000006.00008; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Surgical speciality alumni, 1990; UA225.004.001.000006.00009; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Specialties, Surgical; Slides (photographs)
    - Spectacular Changes, UA225.004.001.000006.00010; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Strengths, UA225.004.001.000006.00011; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Strengths, UA225.004.001.000006.00012; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Andrews, Benjamin, M '14, UA225.004.001.000006.00013; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Andrews, Benjamin F.; M1914
    - ACS tribute to B.F. Andrews, M.D., M '14, UA225.004.001.000006.00014; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Berg, Carl, M '31, UA225.004.001.000006.00015; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Carl, Berg; M1931
    - Dreyfuss, Jack, M '51, UA225.004.001.000006.00016; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Dreyfuss, Jack R.; M1951
    - Faraci, Philip, M '34, UA225.004.001.000006.00017; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Faraci, Philip; M1934
    - George, Ariel, M '06, UA225.004.001.000006.00018; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); George, Ariel; M1906
    - Karp, David, M '34, UA225.004.001.000006.00019; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Karp, David; M1934
    - Karp, David, M.D., UA225.004.001.000006.00020; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Karp, David
    - David Karp with President Mayer and wife, 1986; UA225.004.001.000006.00021; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Richard Kilfoyle, M '43, UA225.004.001.000006.00022; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Kilfoyle, Richard; M1943
    - McGinty, John, M '56, UA225.004.001.000006.00023; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); McGinty, John B.; M1956
    - McGinty, John, M '56, UA225.004.001.000006.00024; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - MacMillan, A.S., M '17, UA225.004.001.000006.00025; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); MacMillan, A. S.; M1971
    - Tom Martin, M '32, with Dr. Crane, UA225.004.001.000006.00026; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Martin, Tom A.; M1932
    - Tom Martin, M '32, with Dr. Crane, UA225.004.001.000006.00027; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Nalebuff, Ed, M '53, UA225.004.001.000006.00028; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Nalebuff, Edward; M1953
    - Nalebuff, Ed, M '53, UA225.004.001.000006.00029; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Photo standing in front of bookshelf
    - Ober, Frank, M '06, UA225.004.001.000006.00030; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Ober, Frank R.; M1906
    - Park, William, M '80, UA225.004.001.000006.00031; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Park, William; M1980
    - Wolfson, Louis, M '19, UA225.004.001.000006.00032; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)